# Mugenzi, Jean Marie

Gasabo KG 648 ST Kigali, Rwanda

Mobile: (+250) 781 990 310 E-mail: <u>mugenzijmv@gmail.com</u> Born in 1995, Male, Rwandan

## **PROFILE**

I am current the **Graphic designer** at Maran Design. With more than 3 years' experience as Graphic designer & frontend/UI Developer, I have worked for different companies and on different projects, creating and maintaining digital assets, such as **graphics**, **images**, **videos**, **interface design**, websites development and testing completed applications. I have a Certificate of Competence in Video Production, Photography & Graphic design that has equipped me with strong multimedia expertise.

## **EDUCATION BACKGROUND**

Period	Field of Study	Institution	Award
2018-2021	Information Technology	IPRC Karongi, Rwanda	Advanced Diploma, A1 in
			Information Technology
2014-2016	A Level, Mathematics,	GS Gihundwe, Rusizi	Advanced Level
	Computer Science and		Certificate (A2)
	Economics		
2011-2013	O Level Education	GS ST Bonaventure, Nkanka	O Level Certificate

## TRAINING AND CERTIFICATES

- Certificate of Competence in Video Production, Photography & Graphic design Kigali International Arts College, 2018.
- 3 months of professional training in ECC (E-Commerce Center) Rwanda as content creator, 2022

#### **TECHINICAL SKILLS**

- Media Production: Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, etc.
- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, ...
- Operating Systems: Linux, Windows
- Databases: SQL Server, MySQL, ORACLE
- **Networking and System Administration:** Cisco Firewalls, VPN Configuration, Server Administration, Linux and Windows Servers.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**, ISOKO250. *FROM JANUARY 2022- PRESENT*

# Key roles and responsibilities:

• Create and maintain digital assets, such as flyers, images, videos, interface design files, wireframes, and interactive mockups.

# BRANDING, INNOVATION AND CREATIVITY MANAGER, JAUSOLUTIONS

FROM JANUARY 2020 TO JANUARY 2022

# **Key Roles and Responsibilities**

- Managing client proposals from typesetting through to design, print and production.
- Working with clients, briefing and advising them with regard to design style, format, print production and timescales.
- Developing concepts, graphics and layouts for product illustrations, company logos and websites.
- Determining size and arrangement of copy and illustrative material, as well as font style and size
- Preparing rough drafts of material based on an agreed brief.
- Reviewing final layouts and suggesting improvements if required.
- Liaising with external printers on a regular basis to ensure deadlines are met and material is printed to the highest quality.

**CONSULTANCIES**, I have worked on different project as a consultant in different companies *FROM JANUARY 2020* 

\_\_\_\_\_

#### JustBetweenUs

JustBetweenUs is a social network base system that provides a way of rotating savings to the trusted individuals who need it across Africa.

## Securis Africa

Securis Africa is particularly aimed at meeting the expectations of companies for which the safety of their employees and customers on the road. I worked at Securis Africa on different projects as Software Developer.

### AIMS Zimbabwe

Is a platform that monitor the workflow of livestock, agriculture, water and land sectors in Zimbabwe.

# FrikaMart

FriMamart is a multinational technology company specializing in e-commerce and retail online.

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

Kinyarwanda, English and French: Spoken, written, and read fluently.

# REFERENCES

Mr. Jaures Habineza	Mobile : (+224) 620 63 19 70 Email : jauhab1@gmail.com	
CEO, Made in Rwanda Online Ltd.		
Mr. Valens Nkubito	Mobile : (+250)788898913	
IT Specialist, Abt Associates Inc.	Email: Valens_Nkubito@pmivectorlink.com	
Mr. Maranatha Habarurena	Mobile: (+250)788462678	
CEO, Maran Design Ltd	Email: marandesign250@gmail.com	

I hereby certify that the above information provided is accurate and true.

Jean Marie Vianney Mugenzi